,geo,text,user,location,entities,sentiment,country
0,,What is God saying to us about #coronavirus ?,petodinice,Lagos,"[('about #', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.231, 'compound': 0.2732}",Nigeria
1,,"BREAKING: ""this is disappointing, but i took the test"". Arsenal's Mikel Arteta tests positive for #coronavirus,  -… ",JerryfranksonJF,"Abuja, Nigeria","[(""Arsenal's Mikel Arteta"", 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.1, 'neu': 0.667, 'pos': 0.233, 'compound': 0.5859}",Nigeria
2,, #Coronavirus testing must be made free to the public if we are going to understand the scope of this crisis. Anything le…,cek422,"Pennsylvania, USA",[],"{'neg': 0.173, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': -0.3767}",USA
3,, Get ready for mass event crowd cancellations across the World starting this weekend: cricket in #Australia in empty st…,InfectiousDz,NYC,"[('World', 'ORG'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.798, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': 0.1779}",USA
4,, The #coronavirus pandemic is revealing just how closely we are all bound together...[A thread] ,vic_gibson,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
5,," COVID-19 update as of this morning:1. Death toll in Italy passes 1,0002. Arsenal's head coach Arteta tests positive3. US…",StewartNgilana,Durban | Port Elizabeth,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('1,0002', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Arteta', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",USA
6,," It’s painful to say, but as an ER doc who talked to  about healthcare, I believe he's uniquely unqualified to…",BWheatnyc,Florida,[],"{'neg': 0.098, 'neu': 0.902, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2382}",USA
7,," 📽️Friends, I will drop another video on Twitter tonight around 7:30pm to answer your questions about #coronavirus.Plea…",LorseaR,"New South Wales, Australia","[('Twitter', 'GPE'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.877, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2732}",Australia
8,," Questions about COVID-19? See this resource and info page from NAfME for music educators, including music instrument hygiene: ht…",straightj23,"Columbus, OH","[('NAfME', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
9,,"How they’re dealing with #coronavirus in a public facility in Portsmouth, Uk. Yes, that’s a coronavirus warning sig… ",_______coolio,"South East, England","['', ('Portsmouth', 'GPE'), ('Uk', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.733, 'pos': 0.141, 'compound': 0.0772}",UK
10,," BREAKING: Democrats proposed 14 days of paid sick leave for workers affected by the #coronavirus, but the Republicans in…",champagneaylin,,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('14 days', 'DATE'), '', ('Republicans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.221, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3716}",
11,, “If we close down all sporting events and we have them played behind closed doors… people are going to go to pubs and all…,YorkLawLondon,UK,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.906, 'pos': 0.094, 'compound': 0.34}",United Kingdom
12,, I pity the poor people who get colds right around now. Not #Coronavirus. Just an old-fashioned cold. They are probably fr…,BeesonMargaret,,[''],"{'neg': 0.227, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6486}",
13,, We’re the heck we’re you the last 6 weeks! AI should have given us a plan #coronavirus,harrytiffanyiv,"Fort Washington, PA","[('the last 6 weeks', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
14,," I don't think she intended to, but Joy asks a very good question here.Yes, , why are you seeking $1B in…",grammyheath,,"[('Joy', 'PERSON'), ('1B', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.628, 'pos': 0.372, 'compound': 0.8883}",
15,," Well written, sourced and data-backed article about the impact and mitigation of COVID-19.Hoping we can all stay safe,…",barbara_ellena,"Christchurch City, New Zealand",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.89, 'pos': 0.11, 'compound': 0.2732}",New Zealand
16,, 1/2 CDC Director Robert Redfield admitted some Americans who seemingly died from influenza were tested positive for novel #coro…,fatal,USA,"[('1/2', 'CARDINAL'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('Robert Redfield', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.139, 'neu': 0.579, 'pos': 0.282, 'compound': 0.4019}",United States
17,," In all seriousness, if you’re stockpiling items you’re hurting people...•Those impacted by #coronavirus can’t get supplie…",pwjkmiller,,[''],"{'neg': 0.218, 'neu': 0.782, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}",
18,, Wash your hands.Wash your hands frequently.Use soap and water.#Coronavirus #COVID19MORE on #Verdict --&gt; …,Mrrandy123RP,"Texas, USA","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
19,, #CoronaVirusCanada #CoronaOutbreak #CoronaVirus  #COVID19 #Ontario's 17 new cases of  include a baby boy: officials …,aliensky0,Worldwide,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), '', ('Ontario', 'ORG'), ('17', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
20,, MUST READ: Joe Biden Plagiarizes President ’s #Coronavirus Plan!,Magz18620939,,"[('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
21,," ""Panic buying"" is pure idiocy, selfish at the very least, and stock-piling toilet rolls is perhaps understandable if you'r…",jiddde,"Ilorin, Nigeria",[],"{'neg': 0.274, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7506}",Nigeria
22,, What a lousy day for USA but we now have a real win- watch  get CDC to say “yes” to covering all #CoronaVi…,DebardiMichael,,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6059}",
23,,  what are your policies for community citizens and your staff in light of the #Covid_19 pan… ,xo_GossipGirl_x,,"[('Covid_19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
24,, Dr. Dena Grayson discusses the latest on #coronavirus.#COVID19 #CoronavirusPandemic ,billymocolorad2,Denver area,"[('Dena Grayson', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
25,, How can the structure of a spike protein found on #coronavirus responsible for the #COVID-19 #outbreak help in its diagnos…,corzine_r,,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.227, 'compound': 0.6124}",
26,," After consulting with top gov health professionals,  has decided to take strong but necessary actions to prot…",rl_faehn,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.809, 'pos': 0.191, 'compound': 0.3716}",
27,,The us government been stealing. It don’t make sense otherwise  #coronavirus,LexUpNext,I wanna go home. 🙁,[''],"{'neg': 0.27, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5719}",Error
28,, My god Jeremy Hunt on Ch4 news looks terrified and clearly disagrees with government line #coronavirus,hocwatch,England,"[('Jeremy Hunt', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.273, 'neu': 0.519, 'pos': 0.208, 'compound': -0.3612}",UK
29,, #BREAKING Universal Studios Hollywood theme park to close for two weeks to help contain #coronavirus,_pulido_nenaa,"Fontana, CA","['', ('BREAKING Universal', 'ORG'), ('Studios Hollywood', 'PERSON'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.162, 'compound': 0.4019}",USA
30,, I’m actually angry about Cheltenham. Such irresponsible selfishness for the sake of a day at the races. Assholes. #Cheltenham…,jamesmartyn60,Galway.,"[('Cheltenham', 'GPE'), ('a day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.476, 'neu': 0.524, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9136}",Ireland
31,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,rcgillan,"New York, USA","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
32,, #CoronavirusExperts saying stock up two weeks worth of food and supplies. Half of people live paycheck to paycheck. Ho…,AD1968F,California / Florida,"['', ('CoronavirusExperts', 'ORG'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Half', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.905, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': 0.2263}",USA
33,," #Coronavirus warning from Italy ""The news media in the US has not captured the severity of what is happening here"" https…",glass_jonathan,Some-Where in Canada,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.107, 'neu': 0.893, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}",Canada
34,, There is no objective evidence of panic in the #FamiliesFirst #CoronaVirus Response Ac or in the Biden and Sanders speeches w…,SFAuGrrl,"San Francisco, CA","['', ('FamiliesFirst', 'ORG'), ('Response Ac', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'GPE'), ('Sanders', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.224, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6705}",USA
35,," So, you’ve probably seen mine and other disabled people’s pissed off tweets about the response to the #CoronaVirus. Y…",worldhopper_os,,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.189, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6369}",
36,," Before #coronavirus, I heard  predict China would not last as a unified state another ten ye… ",Frankapistan,"Nashville, TN","[('China', 'GPE'), ('ten', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.144, 'neu': 0.856, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2924}",USA
37,," Source at HHS says ""Trump political appointees are directly interfering with CDC recommendations for the White House that c…",SharronNiklas,,"[('HHS', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
38,, David Stern would be proud of Adam Silver &amp; his decision to suspend the rest of the  season. It was the correct ca…,WeBeHoopin,🙏🏾The House Kobe Built🙏🏾,"[('David Stern', 'PERSON'), ('Adam Silver &', 'ORG'), ('the  season', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.087, 'neu': 0.795, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': 0.2023}",Error
39,, First was the old lady who lives on the corner that died. But 99 in a 100 would be fine and this way we'd get herd-immunity t…,gmcrotty,"Tullamore, Co Offaly","[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('99', 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.122, 'neu': 0.816, 'pos': 0.061, 'compound': -0.4215}",Ireland
40,,  When it's actually GOP using #Coronavirus crisis to push their partisan political agenda.  GOP are putting…,Happyjam5,"Los Angeles, Ca","[('GOP', 'ORG'), '', ('GOP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.215, 'neu': 0.785, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}",USA
41,,"#Coronavirus in #Romania: 5 Infected, Hospital closed after retired-Cop ignored Safety Measures - Se… ",GregoryGLake,Global,"['', ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hospital', 'ORG'), ('-Cop', 'ORG'), ('Safety Measures - Se', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.318, 'neu': 0.52, 'pos': 0.162, 'compound': -0.4019}",USA
42,,It's Sad That Now We Can't Enjoy Our Fav Sport In Peace. F*CK Whoever Manufactured This Sh*t!#CoronaVirus #CoronavirusPandemic #Covid_19,Cericali_KE,Kenya,"[('Sad That', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Whoever Manufactured', 'WORK_OF_ART'), '']","{'neg': 0.315, 'neu': 0.556, 'pos': 0.13, 'compound': -0.6124}",Kenya
43,, Senator Lindsey Graham has #PaidSickLeave. He can self-isolate for #coronavirus exposure without losing pay. Why can’t every…,jlpcoleman,,"[('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('PaidSickLeave', 'MONEY'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.188, 'compound': 0.357}",
44,, Don't panic #Covid_19 #coronavirus ,KayBee33369775,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.526, 'pos': 0.474, 'compound': 0.4023}",
45,,"BREAKING: Ghana reports first two cases of #coronavirus, patients returned from Norway and Turkey.",2019nCoVwatcher,,"[('Ghana', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
46,, TLDR explains. #coronavirus ,mamandurria1,"Sao Paulo, Brazil",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Brazil
47,," 🚨BREAKING: #Ohio's top health official: ""At the very least 1% of our population is carrying this virus...We have 11.7 mi…",DEJSAM247,"Bloemfontein, South Africa","['', ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('11.7', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.087, 'compound': 0.2023}",South Africa
48,,Top tip: if you are hosting a dinner party and want to make it special on a budget I always find chucking in a few… ,ShaunKReturned,"Birmingham, England",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.667, 'pos': 0.333, 'compound': 0.7579}",UK
49,," This week we are offering video broadcasts and livestreams to share strength, comfort and unity with our community in…",JamesWithers3,"New York, New York","[('This week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.669, 'pos': 0.331, 'compound': 0.7845}",USA
50,, Trump is now doing to America what he did to me and 20 other women. #Coronavirus  #CoronavirusPandemic,NewNewsey,everywhere,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
51,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",mis4nthrope,,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",
52,," Germany, France, Spain, Switzerland, UK and USA are all following the same upward trajectory paths of #coronavirus cases…",dorachandayon,"Toshima-ku,Tokyo,Japan","[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Japan
53,, 🦠 A COVID19 timelime of confirmed cases outside of China until today. How is this crisis affecting your daily life?…,GiovanniMario12,Italia,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.223, 'neu': 0.777, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7073}",Italy
54,, China Has A Campaign To Blame #America For The #CoronaVirusThey Say It Started In The U.S.They Blame #America For Spr…,vito4224,USA,"[('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.22, 'neu': 0.78, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5859}",United States
55,," The last patient in Wuhan has been dispatched, all temporary hospitals have been closed, life is going back to normal! #Co…",Khattarperla,Highgarden,"[('Wuhan', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
56,,...Hope y’all stay safe 🙏🏻 and keep up to date on the CDC or World Health Organization not false info. #COVID19 #coronavirus,Brandon4Brody,"Pueblo, CO","[('CDC', 'ORG'), ('World Health Organization', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.879, 'pos': 0.121, 'compound': 0.4404}",USA
57,, #BREAKING: All Catholic churches across Rome to completely close due to #coronavirus,booksNrulers,Corona & Jamaica ,"[('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
58,, Stay safe.—#Covid19#CoronaVirus#Ghana ,Augustmhern_,"Koforidua, Ghana",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Ghana
59,," #Coronavirus: The Santa Fe Indian School in New Mexico is closing today-classes set to resume April 29. ""The difficult decisio…",vynx,El Lay & Sactown ,"[('The Santa Fe Indian School', 'ORG'), ('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('April 29', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.116, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",Error
60,, Bette with another KO! 👊🏻 💥 #trump #coronavirus # ,FRiGGiNREGAN,,"[('KO', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
61,, Foundations and #coronavirus: three considerations 💭1. Impact on operations2. Impact on causes that foundations suppo…,GrantFunders,"London, England","['', ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
62,,Fear will kill #Coronavirus,RobertPPurcell,"norther New Jersey, USA",[''],"{'neg': 0.798, 'neu': 0.202, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.836}",USA
63,,"Give us this day our daily organic vitamins, and forgive us trusting in synthetic sources, as we forgive China for… ",dahldoc,,"[('this day', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.711, 'pos': 0.289, 'compound': 0.7096}",
64,, An expert team of nine members with 31 tons of medical supplies from China arrived at Italy on Thursday night (local time).…,Lucy87099762,,"[('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('31 tons', 'QUANTITY'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
65,," If you haven't watched  's speech today on how we should respond to #coronavirus, take a few minutes to do so. It i…",SurferSolar,Planet Earth,"[('today', 'DATE'), '', ('a few minutes', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
66,, I am very surprised the UK did not impose more restrictions today. It still thinks we are weeks from the peak of the epidem…,MariosTsoutsouk,"Nottingham, England","[('UK', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.837, 'pos': 0.163, 'compound': 0.4733}",UK
67,, A perfect solution to non contact body temperature measurement for entry and exit screening against #coronavirus! Incorporati…,QCCC_Tom,"Atlanta, GA",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.69, 'pos': 0.31, 'compound': 0.7424}",USA
68,,NYC officials move to debunk online rumor about drastic transit shutdowns due to #coronavirus,News12WC,"Yonkers, NY","[('NYC', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
69,, BREAKING:  and House Dems have proposed a multi-billion dollar #coronavirus package so that workers can stay home…,kiwitrader24,Chicago Burbs,"[('House', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
70,," STATEMENT: On the May Rebellion &amp; #coronavirus. XR – as part of a wider movement – exists to protect life, both now &amp; f…",AcidSwims,he/him,"[('the May Rebellion &amp', 'ORG'), '', ('XR', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.065, 'neu': 0.823, 'pos': 0.113, 'compound': 0.2732}",Error
71,," Well, that explains Trump’s refusal of test kits from the World Health Organization, when 60 other countries were more tha…",ctsong,,"[('Trump’s', 'ORG'), ('the World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('60', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.9, 'pos': 0.1, 'compound': 0.2732}",
72,, How about “because testing is nearly impossible to get”? How about that whether someone currently sick… ,lamarshall,"Durham, NC",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
73,,"Ralph's is currently packed with people terrified of catching #coronavirus, all standing a foot from one another,… ",MartiniGiant,,"[('Ralph', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.211, 'neu': 0.789, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6124}",
74,,  Oh look... it’s the pathologically-lying sociopath who WASTED PRECIOUS WEEKS telling us #coronavirus was a…,tulsabird,"Tulsa, OK",[],"{'neg': 0.184, 'neu': 0.608, 'pos': 0.207, 'compound': 0.128}",USA
75,," A woman in her 60s has died from #coronavirus in #LA County.  reports victim is not from the Southland, but…",SusanTaylorSD,San Diego ,"[('60s', 'DATE'), '', '', ('Southland', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.251, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6908}",USA
76,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,lbpyyz,"Toronto, Ontario","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",Canada
77,, There is no objective evidence of panic in the #FamiliesFirst #CoronaVirus Response Ac or in the Biden and Sanders speeches w…,chaser1066,Sydney Australia,"['', ('FamiliesFirst', 'ORG'), ('Response Ac', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'GPE'), ('Sanders', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.224, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6705}",Australia
78,,"Super proud of our team for delivering very important information to our community, LIVE as it happens. Comprehen… ",JasonViauCBC,"Windsor, Ontario","[('Comprehen', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.623, 'pos': 0.377, 'compound': 0.8439}",Canada
79,," Mr. Jones has been marketing &amp; selling toothpaste, dietary supplements, creams &amp; other products as treatments to preven…",star1965,NYC,"[('Jones', 'PERSON'), ('&amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
80,," BREAKING NEWS: Tune in for updates from Mayor Lightfoot, Governor Pritzker, Cook Co. President Preckwinkle and public…",jokerwoo1220,,"[('Lightfoot', 'PERSON'), ('Pritzker', 'PERSON'), ('Cook Co.', 'ORG'), ('Preckwinkle', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
81,,  We don't know if they are Ghanaian citizens who tested positive for the #coronavirus but they are said to have re…,Onemryeboah,"Sunyani,Ghana","[('Ghanaian', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.897, 'pos': 0.103, 'compound': 0.3182}",Ghana
82,, #Coronavirus crisis has affected an ice-locked Arctic research expedition. A team member tested positive for SARSCoV2. Th…,AndreasKakaris,Proud to be Freak,"['', ('Arctic', 'LOC'), ('SARSCoV2', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.256, 'neu': 0.583, 'pos': 0.161, 'compound': -0.2732}",Error
83,,When you have a gym membership and you can’t use it because you’re “not a student...”?! Like wtf?! … ,Falconyx85,"Elkins, WV",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.813, 'pos': 0.187, 'compound': 0.5337}",USA
84,, Ghana and Gabon confirm first cases of #coronavirus,MiaFarrow,USA ,"[('Ghana', 'PERSON'), ('Gabon', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",United States
85,,"Today’s Update:ITALY: lockdownCHINA: lockdownDENMARK: lockdownNORWAY: lockdownTURKEY: lockdown IRELAND, FRANC… ",PaulN84,Hastings,"[('Today', 'DATE'), ('IRELAND', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
86,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,impeach_him_pls,"South Jersey ,United States","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
87,," Dear Coronavirus, I’m telling you right now....you can have the NBA....take away Soccer, golf, tennis, volleyball, whateve…",tgailporter27,"Carbondale, IL","[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Soccer', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.3818}",USA
88,, #ICYMI ⁦⁩ took a medical director out to the streets of Indianapolis so that he could answer your #Coronav…,CBS4Indy,"Indianapolis, IN","[('Indianapolis', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
89,, New York City's mayor Bill de Blasio has declared a state of emergency to fight the spread of the #coronavirus outbreak - as h…,Kelly4Law,"#Leeds, Yorkshire via #Belfast","[(""New York City's"", 'GPE'), ('Bill de Blasio', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.206, 'neu': 0.794, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6369}",UK
90,, Breaking: The Federal Reserve Bank of New York announced Thursday that it will spend $1.5 trillion to purchase financia…,laithreann,bác,"[('The Federal Reserve Bank', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('$1.5 trillion', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
91,,NY Attorney General threatens legal action if Alex Jones keeps telling viewers his toothpaste can cure #coronavirus ,RawStory,"Washington, DC","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.136, 'neu': 0.785, 'pos': 0.079, 'compound': -0.2732}",USA
92,, President  has taken bold action in response to the #Coronavirus. The steps the President announced in regar…,Lizbethjoy,,"[('Coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.3818}",
93,," After consulting with top gov health professionals,  has decided to take strong but necessary actions to prot…",BikingBluesman,"Richland, MI",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.809, 'pos': 0.191, 'compound': 0.3716}",USA
94,," Jeremy Hunt is on . He looks terrified. He is choosing his words carefully, but says the countries that hav…",CourgetteQueen,UK,"[('Jeremy Hunt', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.12, 'neu': 0.819, 'pos': 0.06, 'compound': -0.3071}",United Kingdom
95,," Sir David Attenborough tells Sky News he hopes the UK delivers concrete action on climate change and isn't ""blown off course""…",DrillSargentLou,,"[('David Attenborough', 'PERSON'), ('Sky News', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.877, 'pos': 0.123, 'compound': 0.4215}",
96,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",johnmerro1,,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",
97,, Ayatollah Khamenei says that there is evidence that the #coronavirus may be a ‘biological attack’ and ordered IRGC to set up…,AlirezaNader,"Washington, DC","['', ('IRGC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
98,," Take the time to watch this, get smart. I'll value the word of a renowned medical professional over reporters who know…",CrownMeEmpress,🤫🕵🏾‍♀️ It's a secret ,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.221, 'compound': 0.6249}",Error
99,," If you haven't watched  's speech today on how we should respond to #coronavirus, take a few minutes to do so. It i…",LeahDaisyD,"Santa Rosa Beach, FL","[('today', 'DATE'), '', ('a few minutes', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
100,, Joe Biden is what a president should sound like and how a president should behave. #PresidentBiden #coronavirus …,LiviaFields5,,"[('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('PresidentBiden', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.848, 'pos': 0.152, 'compound': 0.3612}",
101,, Joe Biden is what a president should sound like and how a president should behave. #PresidentBiden #coronavirus …,AdamRobertCohen,"West Palm Beach, FL","[('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('PresidentBiden', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.848, 'pos': 0.152, 'compound': 0.3612}",USA
102,,"#Coronavirus""Go wash your hand..""👇",Kessunberber,Hors Sol :),[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
103,, #CDCTRAVELNOTICE: #Coronavirus in most of #Europe. CDC recommends avoiding all nonessential travel to most of Europe. More i…,Zachsara,,"['', '', ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.788, 'pos': 0.094, 'compound': -0.128}",
104,, Gonna Be Announcing Each Player Getting #CoronaVirus Like it’s #NBAFreeAgency,Renegades_Hoop,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.783, 'pos': 0.217, 'compound': 0.3612}",
105,," Does anybody else remember that approximately 60 million Americans were infected with the swine flu in 2009? Over 18,00…",bremi,"Pennsylvania, USA","[('approximately 60 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('2009', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.254, 'neu': 0.746, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7003}",USA
106,,"In 1918, the Spanish flu completely destroyed India's economy. What can we learn from it for 2020?1) Stop all lar… ",averagekind,,"[('1918', 'DATE'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.328, 'neu': 0.672, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.807}",
107,,how long before purposely coughing on someone becomes a criminal offense#Covid_19 #coronavirus,Mr_Ant87,"Canberra, ACT, Australia",[''],"{'neg': 0.254, 'neu': 0.746, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",Australia
108,, has lifted the paywall on all articles related to the #coronavirus out of concern for public health. Also… ,nhanson_reports,"Chico, CA",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
109,, Our #FlattenTheCurve graphic is now up on  with proper attribution &amp; a CC-BY-SA licence.  Please share far &amp; wide…,manaurism9,Dominican Republic,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.78, 'pos': 0.22, 'compound': 0.5423}",Dominican Republic
110,,"  🇺🇸 President : ""The future does not belong to #Globalists; it belongs to #Patriots.""…",Patriotlana,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
111,, Dr. Dena Grayson discusses the latest on #coronavirus.#COVID19 #CoronavirusPandemic ,windycityamar,best city in the world,"[('Dena Grayson', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
112,," This is how the British media is responding to Trump’s constant lies about #coronavirus Our media really, really needs…",seany_mac23,,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Trump’s', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.135, 'neu': 0.865, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4215}",
113,," 🚨🚨🚨Things are moving quickly with the #Coronavirus, and I already have an update regarding testing for the virus. Pl…",GrayGinther,,"[('Coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
114,," As a human race we will all get through this! We just have to band together as a community, country, continent, world, as…",businessSavvy13,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
115,,The man stands up for mental health AND is doing his part for his NBA community. Him and Mark Cuban are setting the… ,ReddyRoopa,"Toronto, Canada","[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Mark Cuban', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
116,, Iran's #coronavirus crisis is larger than #China's &amp; #Europe's because the regime is still acting ideological with less re…,KENANDOGAN1,https://www.instagram.com/kena,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), '', ('China', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.186, 'neu': 0.814, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}",Error
117,," Pressure works: after national call for #coronavirus ACTION not delay, McConnell canceled Senate recess. Now pass the damn bi…",Wandacalabrese1,,"['', ('McConnell', 'ORG'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.214, 'neu': 0.7, 'pos': 0.086, 'compound': -0.4475}",
118,," #Coronavirus: UK action plan poised for 'social distancing' phaseDuring parliamentary debate, former health secretar…",Sanyeh1,Argyll and Northamptonshire,"['', ('UK', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.867, 'pos': 0.133, 'compound': 0.25}",UK
119,, does social media distancing flatten the curve? #coronavirus,HeavyFeatherRev,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
120,,Published in March 2019 predicting #coronavirus outbreaks will originate from bats in China. But no one took it (an… ,SiliconHall,Ontario Tech. University,"[('March 2019', 'DATE'), '', ('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",Canada
121,, WATCH: The Serbian president coughs uncontrollably as a journalist asks him a question about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #C…,cmitch2108,,"[('Serbian', 'NORP'), ('about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.161, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",
122,, The only two people in the world who ain't worried about no #coronavirus ,Keat420,"36.7282 N°, 76.5836 W°","[('two', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.744, 'pos': 0.256, 'compound': 0.4168}",Error
123,, Don’t forget to pace your social media consumption around #coronavirus ,LCShah,"Los Angeles, CA",[],"{'neg': 0.174, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2263}",USA
124,, #BREAKING State of Kansas announces first #coronavirus death. Man in his 70s. Lived in a long term care facility in Wyandot…,RalphCSTEM,"Olathe, KS","[('Kansas', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', ('his 70s', 'DATE'), ('Wyandot', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.155, 'neu': 0.717, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': -0.1779}",USA
125,, It never ceases to amaze me to witness the bottomless depths of ’s willful ignorance.#CoronavirusPandemi…,Viccimn,"Somerset, California",[],"{'neg': 0.169, 'neu': 0.831, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.431}",USA
126,, So...here is Rudy touching all the mics following Mondays shoot around that has some people concerned... #TakeNote #utahjazz…,AndyVigil23,,"[('Mondays', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.34}",
127,, We sent a letter to Chicago's mayor and the CPS CEO today regarding their response to the #COVID19 #coronavirus pandemic. We…,GoGoGadgetHoe,Chicago Over Everything.,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('CPS', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
128,, Italy and South Korea saw their first #coronavirus cases in late January but they both had different testing responses and dra…,FenMorgana,,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', ('late January', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
129,,  DONATE NOW to keep  #CA45  in Congress working #ForThePeople!#Covid_19 #Coronavir…,ottawatts,O-H-I-O,"['', ('Congress', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
130,," For accommodations that are REQUIRED BY LAW. So, imagine my surprise (all disabled people’s surprise) when because of…",WYETTHASSP0KEN,D(M)V,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.878, 'pos': 0.122, 'compound': 0.3321}",USA
131,, CORONAVIRUS: THE PHARMA PANDEMIC  Has Big Pharma Primed us for a COVID Disaster?; ICAN’s CDC Lawsuit Under Attack; FOIAs…,annemdewey,,"[('PHARMA', 'ORG'), ('ICAN', 'ORG'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('Under Attack', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.238, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6124}",
132,," So, you’ve probably seen mine and other disabled people’s pissed off tweets about the response to the #CoronaVirus. Y…",buddhacanvas,Stolen Land,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.189, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6369}",Error
133,, These are stressful and uncertain times for the world. Dealing with #coronavirus in both of my worlds of medicine and NHL remi…,kingstchiro,,"['', ('NHL', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.216, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6705}",
134,," This #coronavirus *cannot* be stopped. It can only be slowed.Federal, state, and local officials need to SHUT DOWN EVE…",fringephile,"Oklahoma, USA","[('SHUT DOWN EVE', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.095, 'neu': 0.905, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2263}",USA
135,,#Coronavirus can’t get me if I don’t go to work ,luise_mtz,"Dallas, Texas",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
136,, Jesus Christ. Just learned that the reason Congress hasn’t been able to pass a #coronavirus relief bill yet for workers an…,bluedillygal,America,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.4767}",United States
137,," Gunners, our Manager has #CoronaVirus o!!! 😭  ⚽️",hajiselfpaid,"Lagos, Nigeria","['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Nigeria
138,, Things move fast in two days.  then and now on the #coronavirus. Wow. ,Locke_Rubin,"Limerick, Ireland","[('two days', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.759, 'pos': 0.241, 'compound': 0.5859}",Ireland
139,, WATCH: The Serbian president coughs uncontrollably as a journalist asks him a question about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #C…,debbie2debbie1,saint ,"[('Serbian', 'NORP'), ('about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.161, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",USA
140,," Trump called the #coronavirus outbreak a Democratic ""hoax"" and said it was basically no worse than the flu. So please, yes,…",BooksHockey,"Chicago, IL","[('Trump', 'ORG'), '', ('Democratic', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.298, 'neu': 0.604, 'pos': 0.098, 'compound': -0.6494}",USA
141,, Tom Hanks' son Chet gave an update on his parent’s condition after they tested positive for #CoronaVirus. More: …,xx__alexiss,,"[(""Tom Hanks'"", 'PERSON'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.5574}",
142,,"Dear Kingsway community – As more information about the #coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak in GTA is available, we ar… ",thekingswaybia,"Etobicoke, Toronto, ON, Canada","[('Kingsway', 'GPE'), '', ('GTA', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.3818}",Canada
143,," ""Let me summarize it in 4⃣ key areas.1⃣ Prepare and be ready.2⃣ Detect, protect and treat.3⃣ Reduce transmission.4⃣ Innova…",ryanisarapper,"Inglewood, CA","[('4⃣', 'CARDINAL'), ('Prepare', 'ORG'), ('Detect', 'GPE'), ('Reduce', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.126, 'compound': 0.3818}",USA
144,, The general solution to #coronavirusIs shut everything down short-term in order to save everything long-termIt's EXAC…,AlexDevantier,Melbourne,"['', ('EXAC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.282, 'compound': 0.6705}",Australia
145,, The #coronavirus just ended our Disney vacation!  is closing for the 1st time in the history of the park. We need a un…,simply_samii95,leesville louisiana,"['', ('Disney', 'ORG'), ('1st', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
146,, . launches rapid response #coronavirus test | Center for Discovery and Innovation test reduces wait time from days…,JessPerry_NJ,NJ,"['', ('Center for Discovery', 'ORG'), ('Innovation', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.852, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.3818}",USA
147,, Perioperative Considerations for the 2019 Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19)#Coronavirus #COVID19 #Anesthesia #MedTwitter 🦠…,The_Gracey,Antarctica,"[('2019', 'DATE'), ('COVID-19)#Coronavirus #COVID19 #Anesthesia #', 'MONEY'), ('MedTwitter', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.827, 'pos': 0.173, 'compound': 0.3182}",Antarctica
148,, One Congresswoman interrogated the CDC director to the point he greenlit free #CoronaVirus testing for all Americans: …,xojudith_,"Balearic Islands, Spain","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Congresswoman', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.158, 'compound': 0.1779}",Spain
149,, The #Coronavirus outbreak has led to people panic-buying and clearing shelves. Please consider the elderly and weak - those…,tauloka,Dunya,[],"{'neg': 0.137, 'neu': 0.755, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': -0.1531}",USA
150,, President  has taken bold action in response to the #Coronavirus. The steps the President announced in regar…,Doyle_Media,Sydney • 1.0 AU,"[('Coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.3818}",Australia
151,, Government #coronavirus science advisor Dr David Halpern tells me of plans to ‘cocoon’ vulnerable groups. …,YeahISa1dit,,"['', ('David Halpern', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.119, 'neu': 0.881, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2263}",
152,," The Executive response to #coronavirus has been so mind-blowingly botched, Trump really does need to be permanently linked to…",SheriShepherd16,Chicago ,"['', ('Trump', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
153,," Coronavirus: Death toll surpasses 1,000 in Italy as US suspends travel from Europe #Coronavirus ",obotthiman_kun,日本 東京,"[('1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.231, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",Japan
154,,Disneyland is closed. #truestory #coronavirus ,AVPhenom,"RSM, California","[('Disneyland', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
155,," Trump defends his decision to announce #coronavirus travel restrictions without consulting European officials, saying he had t…",mario76wawpl,war saw,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), '', ('European', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Poland
156,, How can the structure of a spike protein found on #coronavirus responsible for the #COVID-19 #outbreak help in its diagnos…,kath3etto,United States,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.227, 'compound': 0.6124}",United States
157,, Eagles postpone Dallas concert due to #coronavirus concerns:  ,TheMuslimHippie,DMV ,"[('Dallas', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.213, 'neu': 0.787, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2263}",USA
158,,Low key waiting for #SulRoss to cancel classes for the rest of the semester especially since a lot of y’all from #SA 👀 #coronavirus #covid19,RD3taco,"El Paso, TX","[('SulRoss', 'MONEY'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.163, 'neu': 0.837, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}",USA
159,,Oh god... say it isn’t so... wheel of fortune is going to have to play reruns 😭 thanks a lot #coronavirus,ricko_nasty,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.238, 'compound': 0.6486}",
160,," This picture was taken last weekend at Mar-a-Lago. The guy in the hat standing next to Trump is Fábio Wajngarten, press secret…",JanieceStaton,"Beaverton, Oregon, USA","[('last weekend', 'DATE'), ('Mar-a-Lago', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Fábio Wajngarten', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
161,, People of my hometown #Siena sing a popular song from their houses along an empty street to warm their hearts during the…,korkybuczek,Standing at the gate of Vienna,[''],"{'neg': 0.073, 'neu': 0.735, 'pos': 0.192, 'compound': 0.4404}",Austria
162,," The son in law who did not solve the opioid crisis, nor bring peace to the Mideast, and is in charge of the “wall” project n…",forester6291,Long island ny,"[('Mideast', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.271, 'neu': 0.729, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8197}",USA
163,, WATCH: The Serbian president coughs uncontrollably as a journalist asks him a question about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #C…,NTexasRealtor4u,North Texas,"[('Serbian', 'NORP'), ('about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.161, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",USA
164,, .     MUST review  proposed #coronavirus bill very carefully.…,rucofefe,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
165,,Disneyland and Universal Studios closed. Which means Heaven is closed. Which means we are living in Hell on earth.… ,philipo81,,"[('Universal Studios', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.185, 'neu': 0.683, 'pos': 0.133, 'compound': -0.3182}",
166,, Vice President : The vast majority of Americans who contract the #Coronavirus will have flu like symptoms and ful…,GregoryChestnut,"Lilesville, NC","[('Americans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': -0.0258}",USA
167,,I dont think we are going to see any Motorsport for the next few months due to the Coronavirus its far to widesprea… ,PitLanePhoto,"Nantwich, England","[('Motorsport', 'FAC'), ('the next few months', 'DATE'), ('Coronavirus', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
168,,But seriously I Never thought our death 💀 will be made In China 🇨🇳 Too 😞#CoronaVirusUpdate #coronavirus #CoronavirusPandemic,kuamiufresh,Nigeria,"[('China', 'GPE'), '', ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.09, 'neu': 0.743, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.3498}",Nigeria
169,,What do you use to blow your nose? Attempting to see if the answer to this question is why people are stocking up… ,sammyjoxoxo,Wisconsin,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
170,, Kids and parents: You may have heard the word #coronavirus online or on TV. You probably have a lot of questions. Readthis…,njoylife2012,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
171,,This goes to show you how quickly the random #emoji becomes a #sensation 😷🦠🧼#CoronavirusPandemic… ,SpaceKatStrat,"Houston, TX","['', '', ('\U0001f9a0', 'GPE'), '', ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
172,, - 10 cases are under further investigation- 2 cases are listed as 'source not identified'- Cases under investigation - 1…,ThatSugaTaeTae,D⍺ydre⍺ming ℐn ℋope’s Ꮗorℓd ,"[('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Sweden
173,,"Q: Why aren't 🇺🇸 the USA public schools  closed yet ?A: Nobody to babysit the kids GOTTA BE REALISTIC ""… ",PRAISETRIUNEGOD,#worldwide ,"[('🇺', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('GOTTA BE REALISTIC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
174,," Soooo The Economy is about to take a hit and the Democrats answer is to Promise Americans Two weeks of Sick Leave.??Ok,…",Lyddiebugg,United States,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Promise Americans', 'PRODUCT'), ('Two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Sick Leave.??Ok', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.761, 'pos': 0.092, 'compound': -0.3313}",United States
175,, .     MUST review  proposed #coronavirus bill very carefully.…,AaronSims31,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
176,, The UK is currently on the same #coronavirus trajectory as Italy and still we don’t have mass testing. Mass testing has…,Dalma72166898,"Brighton, England","[('UK', 'GPE'), '', ('Italy', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
177,, stop spreading #coronavirus please using the power of the internet to let people know where the person who is confirmed wi…,trueblood_b,ireland,[''],"{'neg': 0.094, 'neu': 0.809, 'pos': 0.098, 'compound': 0.0258}",Ireland
178,," ""We are marshaling the full power of the Federal Government to protect the American people.” - President #…",WooWabi,,"[('the Federal Government', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.3818}",
179,,"Come on , please do the right thing like  and allow rebooking of flights without a fee for… ",raquelquefois,"Sheffield, England",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.66, 'pos': 0.34, 'compound': 0.6908}",UK
180,, 3 years of grad school and this is how it all ends #COVD19 #Coronavirus ,itsanadelrey,,"[('3 years', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
181,, Muslim heros Asiyah and Jawad incredibly give out FREE #Coronavirus kit to the elderly. ,ArtisanPastry,Ontario,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Asiyah', 'GPE'), ('Jawad', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.645, 'pos': 0.355, 'compound': 0.7647}",Canada
182,," Despite suspension of Umrah due to so called created Corona virus and no people allowed in the haram after Isha prayers, Alla…",shateeh_jr,Barcelona/Manchester,"[('Umrah', 'GPE'), ('Corona', 'GPE'), ('Isha', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.09, 'neu': 0.817, 'pos': 0.093, 'compound': 0.0202}",UK
183,, #CDCTRAVELNOTICE: #Coronavirus in most of #Europe. CDC recommends avoiding all nonessential travel to most of Europe. More info…,yonkersoem40,Yonkers NY,"['', '', ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('CDC', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.788, 'pos': 0.094, 'compound': -0.128}",USA
184,, disasters like the #coronavirus will only magnify pre-existing vulnerabilities. we need to be coming together to care for o…,realthecaffiend,"Edmonton, AB",[''],"{'neg': 0.201, 'neu': 0.579, 'pos': 0.22, 'compound': 0.128}",Canada
185,,Sorry but NBA stopped and NCAA cancelled it's season and you are still evaluating WHAT???? … ,neverlooba,"Roma, Lazio","[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('NCAA', 'ORG'), ('season', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.367, 'neu': 0.633, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7149}",Italy
186,," #COVID19mx: Although, unlike the #UnitedStates, #Mexico won’t restrict #international #travel, it postponed #TianguisTu…",lisadianatejeda,🇲🇽🇮🇪,"['', '', '', ('TianguisTu', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.286, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",Error
187,,#coronavirus be like ,YahyaOsmani1,Lebanon,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.444, 'pos': 0.556, 'compound': 0.3612}",Lebanon
188,, Everyone including atheists believe that #Coronavirus exists after being informed even though they haven’t seen it. W…,Abdul_MahmoudG,Somalia,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Somalia
189,, You know how Americans handle their fears? We face them. Thankful  is on this #coronavirus challeng…,60DDT,,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.137, 'neu': 0.683, 'pos': 0.18, 'compound': 0.2263}",
190,, It astounds me how much government have left us muddling through over #coronavirus. They’ve announced a stimulus package…,lcrhms,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.162, 'compound': 0.4767}",
191,, Cardi has a few more questions about the #CoronaVirus 🦠 ,Devilschild666x,,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
192,, So are Jewish people still allowed to do metzitzah b'peh during quarantine or no?  #coronavirus,BhumbleHaveF8h,,"[('Jewish', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.136, 'neu': 0.864, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",
193,, Important! Retweet &amp; SHARE THIS LETTER now from Victims in Italy #CoronaVirus ,robert_veres,. San Diego,"[('Retweet &amp', 'ORG'), ('Victims', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.141, 'neu': 0.551, 'pos': 0.308, 'compound': 0.4069}",USA
194,, Prince Charles says he is struggling not to shake hands because of #Coronavirus Arriving at PrincesTrust awards this afte…,yambastola,Jhapa-Ktm,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('PrincesTrust', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.12, 'neu': 0.686, 'pos': 0.194, 'compound': 0.1823}",Nepal
195,, That’s a very small percentage of American fatalities from #coronavirus! #CalmDown #FactsNotFear #FakeNews #Trump2020 ht…,BillH1059,United States,"[('American', 'NORP'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.244, 'neu': 0.756, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.636}",United States
196,, Dr. Dena Grayson discusses the latest on #coronavirus.#COVID19 #CoronavirusPandemic ,one4allmankind,,"[('Dena Grayson', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
197,,  If Biden thinks appearing in the midst of a crisis to criticize his political opponent is a way to win voters over…,dancingladybug6,America,"[('Biden', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.244, 'neu': 0.618, 'pos': 0.138, 'compound': -0.4404}",United States
198,," This is how the mainstream media sneakily and diabolically pushes Islamophobia. What do mosques, Muslims and Islam have…",WINTUR78,New Delhi,"[('Islamophobia', 'GPE'), ('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
199,, What a lousy day for USA but we now have a real win- watch  get CDC to say “yes” to covering all #CoronaVi…,tygergirl,"Brooklyn, NY","[('USA', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6059}",USA
200,, Trump is now doing to America what he did to me and 20 other women. #Coronavirus  #CoronavirusPandemic,JWFHusker,"Denver, CO","[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
201,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,SEval459,"Santa Rosa, CA","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
202,," 🚨 BREAKING 🚨""We have therefore made the assessment that #COVID19 can be characterized as a pandemic""- #coronavirus http…",gitanalatina07,"Florida, USA","[('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
203,, Class of 2020 graduating on skype. #coronavirus #cuny #suny ,fuckitsxochitl,"Gardena, CA","[('2020', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
204,," Just like rest of Muslims,👇 Zulfikar from ""Indian Occupied Kashmir"" will also be evacuated. We got great…",5OActionExpress,,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('👇 Zulfikar', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.865, 'pos': 0.135, 'compound': 0.3612}",
205,,NYC officials move to debunk online rumor about drastic transit shutdowns due to #coronavirus,News12LI,"Long Island, NY","[('NYC', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
206,, Bill Gates was right !!😳 #CoronavirusPandemic #CoronaOutbreak #CoronaVirusUpdate #coronavirus ,LarryMork1,"Wisconsin, USA","[('Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
207,,"Buhari is not the president of Nigeria, he is the president of corona virus #coronavirus     (RT)",chioma_umekwe,,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
208,," A scathing, damning indictment of the government’s lousy, execrable response to the looming #coronavirus disaster from P…",MancMal,Hull,[''],"{'neg': 0.489, 'neu': 0.511, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8885}",UK
209,," Pornhub will allow people living in Italy to access Pornhub Premium for free throughout the month of March, as the whole coun…",brendizzle__,Riverside County,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Pornhub Premium', 'FAC'), ('the month of March', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.794, 'pos': 0.206, 'compound': 0.6369}",USA
210,," The last patient in Wuhan has been dispatched, all temporary hospitals have been closed, life is going back to normal! #Co…",hajarqist,,"[('Wuhan', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
211,, The teams from Dayton Carroll and Beloit West Branch combined for a photo despite not being able to play their …,branpidg,Brandy@timberlanescomplex.com,"[('Dayton Carroll', 'PERSON'), ('Beloit West Branch', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.882, 'pos': 0.118, 'compound': 0.34}",Error
212,, #Socialism is evil until #WallStreet needs a bailout from the #FederalReserve.#FederalReserveBank #Finance #Coronaviru…,kcin6390,,"[('WallStreet', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.367, 'neu': 0.633, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7003}",
213,, The media are the opposite of helpful when trying to gauge an appropriate response to #coronavirus. They don’t have anything u…,DiamondDuke3,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.877, 'pos': 0.123, 'compound': 0.4215}",
214,, You Got #Coronavirus  ,SupaaFlyChris,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
215,, 🚨#BREAKING: San Francisco Public Schools will close due to #coronavirus for 3 weeks starting 3/16.As a #SFUSD parent I expe…,LindaBernfeld,"Miami, FL","[('BREAKING', 'ORG'), ('San Francisco Public', 'GPE'), '', ('3 weeks', 'DATE'), ('3/16.As', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
216,, It's not just a question of whether you get sick.  More important is eliminating the chance that you end up being a one…,Celia3D,London ,[],"{'neg': 0.13, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.161, 'compound': -0.0534}",UK
217,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,clauvolleyball1,,"[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",
218,,Screencap this.What's the over/under of a world leader dying from #coronavirus?In spite of their access to the… ,718Tv,718,[''],"{'neg': 0.185, 'neu': 0.815, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",USA
219,," #Coronavirus update:  extends spring break 1 week, suspends face-to-face classes for the rest of spring semest…",_kately1,the ohio state university,"[('spring', 'DATE'), ('1 week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.903, 'pos': 0.097, 'compound': 0.128}",USA
220,, Our friends at  have written a comprehensive blog post about what older adults need to know about #coronavirus. Ch…,bb60voices,soon...,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.242, 'compound': 0.6249}",USA
221,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",WagnerSBranco,Curitiba,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",Brazil
222,, Pelosi: “We have to put American families first!”Than she attaches democrat PORK programs to vitally needed #coronavirus legi…,LauraGowens2,United States,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('democrat', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.877, 'pos': 0.123, 'compound': 0.3382}",United States
223,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,Anniewhatever,,"[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",
224,," If you haven't watched  's speech today on how we should respond to #coronavirus, take a few minutes to do so. It i…",cherthedream,,"[('today', 'DATE'), '', ('a few minutes', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
225,, Walt Disney Company closing Disneyland park in California due to #coronavirus; company will pay cast members during the sh…,dieb1948,"Michigan, USA","[('Walt Disney Company', 'ORG'), ('Disneyland', 'GPE'), ('California', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.072, 'neu': 0.928, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}",USA
226,,"Because #coronavirus , no more passing of weed till further notice 😂😂😂 Roll your own shid and finish it#Covid_19… ",999Trillion,S.B CITY,[''],"{'neg': 0.115, 'neu': 0.885, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
227,,Keep in mind that banning gatherings over 250 people means that #FoodBanks and #SoupKitchens are now illegal in CA.… ,CSoloy,"Charlotte, NC","[('250', 'CARDINAL'), ('FoodBanks', 'ORG'), ('SoupKitchens', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5574}",USA
228,,This is a very concerning and uncertain time. This is a fluid situation and the facts are changing hourly. We will… ,baskingntheGlow,New York City,"[('hourly', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.12, 'neu': 0.88, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3535}",USA
229,," There’s a public health crisis in our country.We will not stop fighting for access to free testing, paid emergency leave,…",MarlattRichard,,[],"{'neg': 0.239, 'neu': 0.5, 'pos': 0.261, 'compound': -0.1032}",
230,," ‘When hardship befalls people,they supplicate their Lord,turning to Him in penitence. Then,when He lets them taste His mercy,…",lamaberrou,,[],"{'neg': 0.119, 'neu': 0.881, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3182}",
231,,"A thought: If companies want to help negate the possibility of mass panic about #coronavirus , how's about you do… ",johnzie34,,[],"{'neg': 0.148, 'neu': 0.673, 'pos': 0.179, 'compound': -0.0772}",
232,," Ayatollah Tabrizian, a prominent clergyman &amp; a self-proclaimed expert in “Islamic medicine”, has published the following…",lordofseo,"International waters. SEO Search Engine Land UK SEO, CANADA SEO US SEO SEO FATHER","[('&amp', 'ORG'), ('Islamic', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.3182}",Error
233,, JUST IN: Nancy  announces vote on “Families First” #coronavirus response bill with free testing for all.…,Jenorozco79,,"[('Nancy  ', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.82, 'pos': 0.18, 'compound': 0.5106}",
234,," #SanDiego County Supervisor  announced an advisory for ""all senior citizens age 65 or older to cancel nonessentia…",robbrownvegas,Las Vegas / San Diego,"[('age 65 or older', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.111, 'neu': 0.889, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.25}",USA
235,, We have now updated the #coronavirus story at the WhiskyCast web site to include additional visitors center/tour closings a…,Whiskyraj,Earth or the vicinity of,"['', ('WhiskyCast', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
236,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",_Riyad100,LDN x Essex ,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",Error
237,, Trump is now doing to America what he did to me and 20 other women. #Coronavirus  #CoronavirusPandemic,SherrieCanTweet,,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
238,,I’m reposting this thread translated into English by Dr. on front lines of #coronavirus it’s truly A MUST READ to u… ,Veronicaromm,"New Jersey, USA","[('English', 'LANGUAGE'), '', ('A MUST READ', 'WORK_OF_ART')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.868, 'pos': 0.132, 'compound': 0.4404}",USA
239,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",harryutg,,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",
240,, Given that children and young adults are least at risk from #coronavirus I don’t understand the logic of closing school…,LESLIEBENN1,,[''],"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.896, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2732}",
241,," JUST IN: An American Airlines pilot has tested positive for #coronavirus, according to the airline and a second source fami…",ungubunugu1274,timbuktu,"[('American Airlines', 'ORG'), '', ('second', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.5574}",Mali
242,, Shout out to all the POC and immigrant custodians and workers out there sanitizing and cleaning during #coronavirus—I know…,sandalsmom,🌹@takorolling,"[('Shout', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
243,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",TheBusayor,Um die Welt 🌏,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",Error
244,, 3 of the Maryland #coronavirus patients have fully recovered ,Lord_rene7,,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maryland', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
245,," Ya think⁉️South Korea, population 51 million, is testing more than 20,000  individuals a day.Texas, population 28 million,…",csloball,O-H I-O  retweets are not endorsements,"[('Korea', 'GPE'), ('51 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 20,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('28 million', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
246,," Ohio estimates it has more than 100,000 infected with #coronavirus ",bnme13isaac,USA🇺🇸,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('more than 100,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.278, 'neu': 0.722, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5367}",Error
247,," Mikel Arteta: ""This is really disappointing but I took the test after feeling poorly. I will be at work as soon as I’m…",OAlmasri,,[],"{'neg': 0.098, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.076, 'compound': -0.1272}",
248,,#Coronavirus is overrated ,Joe_Shema,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
249,, Some of you have never spent 2 weeks indoors for a game launch and it shows. #coronavirus,hiker_miker,"Lakewood, CO","[('2 weeks', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
250,,"  The Republican Governor for Ohio Mike DeWine just confirmed that only 1,000 tests are available to 11.69 Mil…",CoronaVirusCall,North America,"[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Mike DeWine', 'PERSON'), ('only 1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('11.69', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",North America
251,," In response to COVID-19, Japan is going to start paying parents $80 a day to stay home from work and take care of their…",hystericaldyke,she/her // pdx,"[('COVID-19', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('80', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4939}",USA
252,, Wash your hands.Wash your hands frequently.Use soap and water.#Coronavirus #COVID19MORE on #Verdict --&gt; …,Karla380W1990,"Kent, Wa","['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
253,," Children burn shoes to heat water outside Mohammad Shehab Camp, an informal Syrian refugee settlement in the Bekaa Valley, Leb…",Schrader_Adam,"Manhattan, NY","[('Mohammad Shehab Camp', 'FAC'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('the Bekaa Valley', 'LOC'), ('Leb', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
254,," As sales of disposable mask sales surges amid the #coronavirus outbreak, single-use face masks are washing up on Hong Kong's b…",mrpropertyplug,"Lakeland Heights, TX","['', (""Hong Kong's"", 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
255,," As a human race we will all get through this! We just have to band together as a community, country, continent, world, as…",KingDaddyDom13,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
256,,Watch 's broadcast: A friend in Italy reporting on what Coronavius does - STOP listening to the U.K govt.… ,AliveInHistory,USA ΔΣΘ 🔺🐘🔺#JTribe #JanFam,"[('Watch', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Coronavius', 'PERSON'), ('U.K', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.139, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.151, 'compound': 0.0688}",Error
257,, More people died in the city of Chicago over the weekend (due to some dem’s corruption &amp; addiction to power over people) th…,JCT5555,,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('the weekend', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5965}",
258,,"They're canceling events everywhere, closing businesses, schools, churches, limiting gatherings of less than 250 pe… ",DJTwinSpin,San Francisco,"[('less than 250', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
259,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",TorqueyLunatico,Not outer space,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",United States
260,, Boy sent home from school after being caught charging kids to use hand sanitiser #coronavirus …,CoochieLover24,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.814, 'pos': 0.186, 'compound': 0.4939}",
261,,Too early ...?  #ClimateEmergency #ClimateChange #coronavirus #CoronaVirusUpdate #ClimateChangeIsReal… ,HJeppesen,"New York, NY",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
262,," The son in law who did not solve the opioid crisis, nor bring peace to the Mideast, and is in charge of the “wall” project n…",MaryKeithBare1,Ohio,"[('Mideast', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.271, 'neu': 0.729, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8197}",USA
263,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,jonathangarcia,"Orlando, FL","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
264,, What to expect from #COVID19 quarantine in #Ethiopia: a thread. I was hospitalised for 3 days in the National…,mebre22,,"[('COVID19', 'MONEY'), '', ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('3 days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
265,, For anyone careering around the supermarkets with heaped trolleys please think of people depending on welfare or who have li…,maryjolley10,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.892, 'pos': 0.108, 'compound': 0.3182}",
266,," Mikel Arteta: ""This is really disappointing but I took the test after feeling poorly. I will be at work as soon as I’m…",chris_nduti,,[],"{'neg': 0.098, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.076, 'compound': -0.1272}",
267,," What did I tell ya?Like flies, they are dropping. #Coronavirus is being used as part of their ""deal"" to cooperate wi…",QQQAnon513,OH,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
268,, #COVID19 impact on #education so far:⛔️376.9 million students out of school worldwide.➡️26 countries have ordered nationwid…,angieram06,,"[('COVID19', 'MONEY'), '', ('million', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
269,, What a lousy day for USA but we now have a real win- watch  get CDC to say “yes” to covering all #CoronaVi…,kissy_jean,"Elk Grove, CA","[('USA', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6059}",USA
270,, Beware of 'Coronavirus Maps' !!!Are you tracking the outbreak or leading hackers directly into your computers?Cyber…,imsrkrishna,"Hyderabad, India",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
271,, If the #coronavirus has taught us anything it is the lengths people will go to when desperate. Next time you want to judge bo…,thecerealquest,Alderholt,[''],"{'neg': 0.09, 'neu': 0.859, 'pos': 0.051, 'compound': -0.25}",UK
272,, 1/ The largest public health lab in Texas is able to conduct a maximum of just 26 coronavirus tests per day. Texas is a…,AthenaSidiropo2,---,"[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Texas', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
273,," Wearing a mask, Brazil President Bolsonaro says he expects #coronavirus test result in hours: ",BrynasSmile,"San Antonio, TX","[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), '', ('hours', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
274,, 'Many more families are going to lose loved ones.'- Johnson.People who voted for Boris are now dying due to his ina…,twilouhom,"London, England","[('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Boris', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.105, 'neu': 0.742, 'pos': 0.152, 'compound': 0.296}",UK
275,,"  The Republican Governor for Ohio Mike DeWine just confirmed that only 1,000 tests are available to 11.69 Mil…",GenetBataiile,"New Hampshire, USA","[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Mike DeWine', 'PERSON'), ('only 1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('11.69', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
276,," Deserted #Rome: late afternoon view of the normally bustling #TreviFountain, #SpanishSteps &amp; #PiazzaNavona - cleared by #cor…",ColettaFrank,Sydney NSW Australia,"[('Rome', 'GPE'), ('late afternoon', 'TIME'), '', ('SpanishSteps &amp', 'ORG'), '', ('PiazzaNavona', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.915, 'pos': 0.085, 'compound': 0.1027}",Australia
277,," France will, from next week, close all nurseries, schools and universities to try to curb the spread of #coronavirus, Presiden…",linanlovelife,"London, England","[('France', 'GPE'), ('next week', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
278,,Arsenal vs Brighton Premier league match slated for Saturday has been postponed after Mikel Arteta tested positive… ,metrotvgh,"Greater Accra, Ghana","[('Brighton Premier', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Mikel Arteta', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.101, 'neu': 0.899, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2023}",Ghana
279,," You know what hasn't been canceled due to #coronavirus? ICE raids. Yup, they are still in the streets putting people in d…",painting_tlc,"Denver, CO","['', ('ICE', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
280,,There you. That’s why we don’t have enough tests. #MonsterTrump #Coronavirus ,honespotus16,"Hodgenville, KY",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
281,, What a lousy day for USA but we now have a real win- watch  get CDC to say “yes” to covering all #CoronaVi…,mvwinall,East Coast,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6059}",United States
282,," Don't you see: The photo to the right shows a Thunder storm; while the #Coronavirus drama is happening, arrests are happening…",PattiClaxton,Washington ,[''],"{'neg': 0.132, 'neu': 0.868, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}",USA
283,, I ordered Alex Jones to immediately stop selling &amp; marketing products as a treatment or cure for #coronavirus on his we…,vodblu,"California, USA","[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}",USA
284,,Last beer tonight with my friends as work moves toward social distancing protocols and implements a total work from… ,organictech551,Northern hemisphere,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.846, 'pos': 0.154, 'compound': 0.4767}",USA
285,, A question for you Boris Johnson as you didn't answer on TV How old is old to you? Fed up with the lies. Don't leave yo…,GlynnAtkinson1,"North East, England","[('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Fed', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.853, 'pos': 0.043, 'compound': -0.3923}",Error
286,,I just got tested positive for the coronavirus 🤒Scariest shit in my life bruh #help #coronavirus… ,KesonnYT,Tilted Towers🧩,"[('🤒Scariest', 'LOC')]","{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.644, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
287,," #coronavirus USA 6:37 pm March 12, 2020Total cases: 1686Total deaths: 40 ",stablegeniusinc,,"['', ('March 12', 'DATE'), ('1686Total', 'CARDINAL'), ('40', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
288,,"Now that some are taking it seriously, #Covid_19 is the proper nomenclature; #coronavirus conjures up misleading im… ",ijiLaw,"Los Angeles, CA","[('Covid_19', 'MONEY'), '']","{'neg': 0.227, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",USA
289,,Are we sure March Madness is cancelled? Seems like it’s in full effect to me. #coronavirus #Covid_19 #MarchMadness,MaxFinnance,(Mostly) CT,"[('March Madness', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.207, 'neu': 0.591, 'pos': 0.203, 'compound': -0.0258}",USA
290,, More people died in the city of Chicago over the weekend (due to some dem’s corruption &amp; addiction to power over people) th…,spkerr333,At my assigned position.,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('the weekend', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5965}",Error
291,," The last patient in Wuhan has been dispatched, all temporary hospitals have been closed, life is going back to normal! #Co…",hafezfirdaus,,"[('Wuhan', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
292,," Italy, today.I can’t believe my eyes.#CoronaVirusUpdate #COVID19 #coronavirus ",Soothe888,"Rome, Italy ~ Shanghai, China","[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Italy
293,, The Tigard-Tualatin School District Board of Directors has called an emergency meeting for 5pm. We’re told this has to d…,MitchFrom503,"Oregon, USA","[('5pm', 'QUANTITY')]","{'neg': 0.12, 'neu': 0.88, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",USA
294,, Lewis Hamilton taking a decisive public stance in calling out the F1 bosses by saying Sunday’s Australian GP shouldn’t be go…,WaterWolfAlex,California,"[('Lewis Hamilton', 'PERSON'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Australian GP', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.909, 'pos': 0.091, 'compound': 0.2263}",USA
295,, The best way to prevent the spread of #COVID19 and other respiratory infections is to wash your hands often with soap and…,NCaDaPi,I'm right here,"[('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.791, 'pos': 0.209, 'compound': 0.6486}",Error
296,," BREAKING Italian medical chief, Roberto Stella, 67, dies from #coronavirus due to respiratory failure#COVID19  https:…",Mick11113,,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Roberto Stella', 'PERSON'), ('67', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
297,," 🚨 BREAKING 🚨""We have therefore made the assessment that #COVID19 can be characterized as a pandemic""- #coronavirus http…",GaddadVinay,Bangalore,"[('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",India
298,, Every Senator and Representative has #PaidSickLeave.  They must vote for the #FamiliesFirst #CoronaVirus Response Act so the…,Wandacalabrese1,,"[('Representative', 'ORG'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
299,, UK Government are exposing more people to getting infected with COVID19 by delaying lockdowns (Lockdowns that WILL be…,nashvrem,,"[('COVID19', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.249, 'neu': 0.751, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6486}",
300,,Why are so many people dying of #Covid_19 in Italy? Very high rates. Police in Italy are patrolling streets with dr… ,Johnnybowe_,,"['', ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
301,, Why the heck is #Biden2020 speaking on the #coronavirus IN AN EFFORT TO BASH ?Democrats &amp; #Biden spew hatred &amp; divisiv…,OneCauseATATime,Ca,"['', ('BASH', 'ORG'), ('Democrats &amp', 'ORG'), ('Biden', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.174, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6369}",USA
302,," Mikel Arteta: ""This is really disappointing but I took the test after feeling poorly. I will be at work as soon as I’m…",yurichandraa,Jakarta,[],"{'neg': 0.098, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.076, 'compound': -0.1272}",Indonesia
303,, #PopeFrancis prays for governments and civil authorities as they seek to deal with the #coronavirus pandemic. #Mass #Homil…,bluebirdtrini,Garden of my thoughts 24/7 = Dangerous,"['', ('PopeFrancis', 'ORG'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.124, 'compound': 0.34}",Error
304,, everything’s cancelled and i’m bored af so here’s a few of my songs with a #coronavirus rewrite. a thread..,_tifffaaanny_,"Covington, GA","[('’s', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.227, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}",USA
305,, Tom Hanks' son Chet gave an update on his parent’s condition after they tested positive for #CoronaVirus. More: …,IvLincoln,,"[(""Tom Hanks'"", 'PERSON'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.5574}",
306,," If you think you may have been exposed to the #coronavirus, please call your health care provider FIRST before showing…",ghcsupclerk19,,[''],"{'neg': 0.055, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.231, 'compound': 0.6369}",
307,, Did i just hear that correctly.??Pelosi has Abortion Funding in this Bill.??#CoronavirusPandemic #coronavirus,flatfeetaxsvc,San Diego | Los Angeles | USA,"[('Abortion Funding', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
308,," Call it a hunch but I'm guessing a ""man"" who has unprotected sex with a porn star doesn't wash his hands regularly or c…",johnboston76,"Boston, MA",[],"{'neg': 0.14, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5023}",USA
309,, Liberals are being majestically lame. It's not racist to call it like it is. The #Coronavirus. 🦠 #MadeInChina https:…,Dani06548474,,"[('Coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.119, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.243, 'compound': 0.4442}",
310,, #Coronavirus testing must be made free to the public if we are going to understand the scope of this crisis. Anything le…,bwadre,"Atlanta, GA",[],"{'neg': 0.173, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': -0.3767}",USA
311,, Streets in Milan and Venice were nearly deserted as Italy added new restrictions to a lockdown imposed to fight #coronavirus h…,Chlumani,,"[('Milan', 'GPE'), ('Venice', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}",
312,, What a lousy day for USA but we now have a real win- watch  get CDC to say “yes” to covering all #CoronaVi…,MicheleDiane8,United States,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('CDC', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.718, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6059}",United States
313,, Insensitive and inhumane #Princewilliam  #Coronavirus ,omghwddgthr,Planet Earth,"['', ('Princewilliam', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.322, 'neu': 0.678, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.2263}",USA
314,," . said: The bad thing is that   didn’t talk to Republicans or the president about it, and they’re…",AlfordJp,,"[('Republicans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.179, 'neu': 0.821, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}",
315,, still has no program in place at JFK for intl arrivals!! What abt other airports around the US?!?!  Total… ,NoplaceReally,Ha-shikkuts Meshomem,"[('JFK', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.172, 'neu': 0.828, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5759}",Error
316,," Take the time to watch this, get smart. I'll value the word of a renowned medical professional over reporters who know…",donnadoll38,"Wickliffe, OH",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.221, 'compound': 0.6249}",USA
317,, here's a brief guide i made about #coronavirus. it covers:- how to protect yourself- symptoms- risk factors- #flatte…,jay_notjay,"Cebu, Philippines","[('about #', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.112, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.139, 'compound': 0.128}",Philippines
318,,Contagion the Drinking game! Grab a Corona and the 2011 film and get your paranoia about Coronavirus amped up!… ,HumanEchoes,,"[('Corona', 'GPE'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('Coronavirus', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.259, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6792}",
319,," Covid-19 interactive map (using R with shiny, leaflet and dplyr): #CoronavirusPandemic #CoronaOut…",_RMlg,"Málaga, España",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Spain
320,, WTH? Pelosi trys to take credit for President  &amp; 's proposal on March 9th for paid leave &amp; free #coro…,MrASTM,,"[('March 9th', 'DATE'), ('&amp', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.196, 'neu': 0.588, 'pos': 0.217, 'compound': 0.1449}",
321,,DOW JONES IS DOWN 8000 POINTS SINCE FEBRUARY ONE.  That darn Obama.  Oh hey wait a minute Obama is not president an… ,MLHarrisAuthor,"Tampa, FL","[('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('a minute', 'TIME'), ('Obama', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
322,,COVID-19 #CoronaVirus Infographic Datapack — Information is Beautiful ,Coach_ChrisOC,"Fall City, WA","[('CoronaVirus Infographic Datapack', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.606, 'pos': 0.394, 'compound': 0.5994}",USA
323,," For accommodations that are REQUIRED BY LAW. So, imagine my surprise (all disabled people’s surprise) when because of…",HufflepuffLord,"Gilbert, AZ",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.878, 'pos': 0.122, 'compound': 0.3321}",USA
324,, President  announces that he is suspending all travel from Europe to the United States for the next 30 days.…,Doyle_Media,Sydney • 1.0 AU,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('the next 30 days', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.865, 'pos': 0.135, 'compound': 0.4215}",Australia
325,,"Listen to this crazy idea. If we all had a livable wage, access to health insurance, paid time off, and there was a… ",sciencewithroge,"Omaha, NE",[],"{'neg': 0.116, 'neu': 0.884, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4118}",USA
326,,Just left #SamsClub...Is it really a good idea to have food samples out right now? 🦠🤔  … ,greenmonstah4,Hawaii/San Francisco/Cape Cod,"[('SamsClub', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.814, 'pos': 0.186, 'compound': 0.4927}",USA
327,, The Government's handling of the #coronavirus outbreak. #CobraMeeting ,North_Hants4eu,"Hampshire, UK","['', ('CobraMeeting', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
328,, BREAKING: The Met is closing due to #coronavirus.,HerbScribner,"Salt Lake City, UT",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
329,," Starting tonight at 7:30pm PDT we are offering video broadcasts and livestreams to share strength, comfort and unity w…",Nanbits,NYC,"[('tonight', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.669, 'pos': 0.331, 'compound': 0.7845}",USA
330,," So, you’ve probably seen mine and other disabled people’s pissed off tweets about the response to the #CoronaVirus. Y…",ice_witch_13,Xadia,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.189, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6369}",Error
331,,"Last week was non-stop memes. It’s all fun &amp; bants until the #CoronaVirus threat comes to your country, city &amp; even… ",Majstar7,"Leicester, England","[('Last week', 'DATE'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.132, 'neu': 0.739, 'pos': 0.128, 'compound': -0.0258}",UK
332,," SOUTH KOREA𝗧𝗘𝗦𝗧𝗦 𝟭𝟭,𝟬𝟬𝟬 𝗣𝗘𝗢𝗣𝗟𝗘 𝗔 𝗗𝗔𝗬 𝗙𝗢𝗥 #𝗖𝗢𝗥𝗢𝗡𝗔𝗩𝗜𝗥𝗨𝗦Spends 13.45% of budget on Health  USA:𝗧𝗘𝗦𝗧𝗦 𝟭𝟭,𝟬𝟬𝟬 𝗶𝗻 𝟯 𝗠𝗢𝗡𝗧𝗛𝗦 𝗼𝗻 #𝗖𝗢𝗥𝗢…",akhilnayak007,,"[('𝗗𝗔𝗬', 'ORG'), ('13.45%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
333,,i’m just happy i don’t have to half time for my basketball team anymore 🤧🦠👉🏻👈🏻 #coronavirus,kayyyleighhhhhh,,"[('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('\U0001f9a0', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.791, 'pos': 0.209, 'compound': 0.5719}",
334,,Socialist measures within a capitalist society can exist. The actions being taken now even by Trump show that socia… ,jackiechaannn,"Boston, MA","[('Trump', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
335,, The  has started a #coronavirus newsletter for a gathering place for our stories and information you may…,michaeldeeds,Boise,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
336,," #BREAKING: Congress Shuts Down U.S. Capitol, House, Senate Offices To Public Until April 1, Amid #Coronavirus Spread ht…",Lizbethjoy,,"['', ('BREAKING', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Shuts Down', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('House', 'ORG'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('April 1', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
337,," SEEN IN KIGALI: To prevent the risk of #Coronavirus outbreak, passengers at the Kigali Bus Park have to wash their hand…",rae05201,,"['', ('the Kigali Bus Park', 'FAC')]","{'neg': 0.095, 'neu': 0.856, 'pos': 0.05, 'compound': -0.25}",
338,," Do Not Panic , Take proper preparation. Let’s play our role , Wash your hands frequently, follow all instructions by …",Abhishek1025,India,"[('’s', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.242, 'compound': 0.6251}",India
339,, co-quarantined with an abuser? worried about having to self-isolate from #coronavirus in a dangerous home situation? Please…,starincali,,[''],"{'neg': 0.416, 'neu': 0.584, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8504}",
340,," #Coronavirus update:  extends spring break 1 week, suspends face-to-face classes for the rest of spring semest…",gabe_t,Columbus Ohio,"[('spring', 'DATE'), ('1 week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.903, 'pos': 0.097, 'compound': 0.128}",USA
341,," JUST IN: An American Airlines pilot has tested positive for #coronavirus, according to the airline and a second source fami…",Sunni_in_SoCal,"Cali, Brooklyn, Vegas","[('American Airlines', 'ORG'), '', ('second', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.5574}",USA
342,, It turns out that the toilet paper issue we have here is happening all over the world!!! Why ?? Why to… ,paranoidpal,Ohio USA,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
343,,"  you must do everything in your power to protect South Africans, especially our impoverished communities…",BarbieROARS,非洲,"[('South Africans', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.843, 'pos': 0.157, 'compound': 0.3818}",Africa
344,," COVID-19 update as of this morning:1. Death toll in Italy passes 1,0002. Arsenal's head coach Arteta tests positive3. US…",jessereignz,South Africa,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('1,0002', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Arteta', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}",South Africa
345,," France will, from next week, close all nurseries, schools and universities to try to curb the spread of #coronavirus, Presiden…",dampagne,"Lagos, Nigeria","[('France', 'GPE'), ('next week', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Nigeria
346,," I wish adults would act like adults &amp; stop this unnecessary, insane panic.  Cancelling spring break. Cancelling #Marc…",MAGAMCAGA1,USA ,"[('&amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.437, 'neu': 0.37, 'pos': 0.193, 'compound': -0.6808}",United States
347,, You can't even get the basics right!Wales has its own Chief Medical Officer as does Scotland and................. Englan…,gwpurnell,Edinburgh,"[('Scotland', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
348,, Here's what you need to know about self-quarantine. #Coronavirus ,nrlaisyahh,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
349,,Broadway Cancels All Performances Until April 13 Due to #Coronavirus Concerns  | Such sad ne… ,alswrite,Motown,"[('April 13', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.294, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6124}",USA
350,, DISNEYLAND CLOSED FOR CORONAVIRUS #Disneyland #coronavirus #Disney #DisneyParks #DisneylandClosed…,arudarinngu,今期1番面白いアニメはダーウィンズゲームです。,"['', ('DisneylandClosed', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
351,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",ActuallyAIex,The Jersey Shore,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",USA
352,, Ignorant “boys with toys” need to grow up and go home! Shut it all down now. Danger to our communities… ,clearticulation,,[],"{'neg': 0.243, 'neu': 0.757, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6996}",
353,,If you can’t beat them... #NewProfilePic #Covid_19 #coronavirus ,M_Shass,Europa league ,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Switzerland
354,, History will not be kind over Boris Johnson's handling of the #Coronavirus crisis. His govt have destroyed NHS resilience.…,Petehof,,"[(""Boris Johnson's"", 'PERSON'), '', ('NHS', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.386, 'neu': 0.614, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8772}",
355,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",LakeElysia,The Elysian Fields,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",USA
356,, Has Johnson government been complacent in its response to Coronavirus (#CODVID19) so far? “Wasted a month” ... “trea…,BindeshM,,"[('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Coronavirus', 'GPE'), ('CODVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.075, 'neu': 0.925, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.0772}",
357,," ⚠️Insurance companies will waive copayments for #coronavirus testing but NOT for treatment.In most states, people with…",BeverlyFolkers,Illinois,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
358,," Source at State Department says ""we are forced to run around like headless chickens because there is 0 leadership by Trump…",umikomorebi,https://t.co/WMK7OtCVMe,"[('State Department', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.128, 'neu': 0.766, 'pos': 0.106, 'compound': -0.128}",Error
359,, #CoronaVirus meets :U.S. Senator  introduces bill to protect voters &amp; elections against inf…,RebeccaWethman,,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.3818}",
360,, Stay safe.—#Covid19#CoronaVirus#Ghana ,CypherDavid,"Tema, Ghana",[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Ghana
361,," New deadly #coronavirus not infectious enough to pose global threat, researchers say ",PaddysMad,Bramall Lane Home Of Football,[''],"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.764, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5267}",UK
362,, In a few minutes Anonymous Bites Back is live with a new #CoronaVirus special.Subject: European DawnStream:https:…,YourMarkLubbers,Mark @ Anonymous Bites Back,"[('a few minutes', 'TIME'), ('Anonymous Bites Back', 'PERSON'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), ('European DawnStream', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
363,, More people died in the city of Chicago over the weekend (due to some dem’s corruption &amp; addiction to power over people) th…,SueSuebarker12,Smoky Mountains,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('the weekend', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5965}",United States
364,," A charter flight carrying a 9-member Chinese aid team, along with tonnes of medical supplies, arrived at #Rome's Fiumi…",red__RD,,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Rome', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
365,, Trump is now doing to America what he did to me and 20 other women. #Coronavirus  #CoronavirusPandemic,B_rad_mmc,,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
366,, President : I restricted travel to prevent American deaths from #Coronavirus ,Rosebud46607781,"Covington, LA","[('American', 'NORP'), '']","{'neg': 0.243, 'neu': 0.654, 'pos': 0.103, 'compound': -0.3612}",USA
367,,"MIT biologist Dr. Ayyadurai performs research nearly every day on the immune system, says the  #coronavirus fear mo… ",JoyLinPark,"Sierra Nevada Foothills, CA","[('MIT', 'ORG'), ('Ayyadurai', 'PERSON'), ('nearly every day', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.748, 'pos': 0.103, 'compound': -0.25}",USA
368,," Saitama City being an absolute piece of shit. With the #COVID19 / #coronavirus happening, Saitama City gave out boxes of…",goofyfootgaijin,Japan,"[('Saitama City', 'GPE'), '', ('Saitama City', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.167, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5574}",Japan
369,, I still look to #SouthKorea as the most instructive example of how to handle the #COVID19 #Coronavirus outbreak. Massive scre…,SusanSeaside,New England,"[('SouthKorea', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
370,, Watch this video to learn how you can help prevent the spread of respiratory diseases like the novel #coronavirus (#COVID19). T…,corzine_r,,"['', ('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.336, 'compound': 0.765}",
371,, Cartoon on #coronavirus #TrumpVirus #Trump2020 #Trumpspeech ,junglejimmy1,"Victoria, British Columbia",[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Canada
372,, BREAKING:  just got CDC Director Redfield to commit to using his authority under existing law to make #Covi…,RVHugs,"Missouri, USA","[('CDC', 'ORG'), ('Redfield', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.821, 'pos': 0.179, 'compound': 0.3612}",USA
373,, Amazing. Fed announced financial market intervention of more than a TRILLION dollars and markets are back down more than 7%.…,Brwnidgl333,Nevada,"[('Fed', 'ORG'), ('more than a TRILLION dollars', 'MONEY'), ('more than 7%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.174, 'compound': 0.5859}",USA
374,, BREAKING:   ALL public schools in Maryland are closed March 16 through March 27.Gatherings of more than 250 people are n…,rj1975,Tarheel Territory ,"[('Maryland', 'GPE'), ('March 16 through March', 'DATE'), ('more than 250', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
375,,Yall over exaggerating over this whole coronavirus shit calm tf down i dont see anyone canceling the nba because of… ,Pablomtz16_pm,,[],"{'neg': 0.225, 'neu': 0.678, 'pos': 0.097, 'compound': -0.4588}",
376,," Very considerate cancellation of the international  Grand Prix so that sports fans in Melbourne, Australia, are not i…",Asian_Football,Asia,"[('Melbourne', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.721, 'pos': 0.279, 'compound': 0.7346}",Asia
377,," Congress must pass the “Families First Coronavirus Response Act” that includes vital funding for free #coronavirus testing, incr…",TFDWofficial,"Tennessee, USA","[('Congress', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.744, 'pos': 0.256, 'compound': 0.6705}",USA
378,, WATCH: The Serbian president coughs uncontrollably as a journalist asks him a question about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #C…,CorblynD,,"[('Serbian', 'NORP'), ('about #coronavirus.😳#COVID19 #', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.161, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3612}",
379,," Since there is some evidence that this may be a ‘#BiologicalAttack,’ the establishment of this Base in the Armed Forces fo…",Giovanni1DiMaio,"Caserta, Campania","[('BiologicalAttack', 'ORG'), ('Base', 'LOC'), ('the Armed Forces fo…', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Italy
380,," WATCH THIS  just now. America has administered 11,000 #coronavirus tests. South Korea has administered 200,000. Ameri…",me_sheer_,,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('200,000', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
381,, Fear Is Driving #coronavirus Narrative.The Fake News Medias are driving this narrative. You should more fearful of the Fake N…,freidablancha12,,[''],"{'neg': 0.446, 'neu': 0.554, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9168}",
382,, Our #FlattenTheCurve graphic is now up on  with proper attribution &amp; a CC-BY-SA licence.  Please share far &amp; wide…,kittybabygoo,United States,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.78, 'pos': 0.22, 'compound': 0.5423}",United States
383,, Everyone-even atheists-believe that #Coronavirus exists without having to prove it or see itThe reason being1 It’s signs…,only1santana_,"London, England","[('Coronavirus', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
384,," Two weeks ago, when #Nigeria recorded its index case of the #coronavirus, I had cause to urge the Federal Government to restrict…",Em_BaTsari,"Katsina, Nigeria 🇳🇬 ","[('Two weeks ago', 'DATE'), ('Nigeria', 'ORG'), '', ('the Federal Government', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Nigeria
385,, Disclaimer: I am NOT an expret in this field. Hope this helps with understanding the last #CoronaVirus chart. #SciArt #S…,lorelayf,"Guayaquil, Ecuador","[('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.742, 'pos': 0.258, 'compound': 0.7096}",Ecuador
386,, BREAKING: JUST IN: NEW YORK CITY MAYOR BILL DE BLASIO DECLARES STATE OF EMERGENCY IN CITY AMID #CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK,stoppression,"Hyderabad, India","[('NEW YORK', 'GPE'), ('BILL DE', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.874, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3818}",India
387,,She. Is. A. Beast. Put her in a higher position of power. #CDC #CommittoTesting #coronavirus  Thank… ,ottawatts,O-H-I-O,"[('A. Beast', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
388,,Tragic for #Americans #DonaldTrump is the very worst person to handle the #coronavirus crisis ,RosieEmery,"Ottawa, Ontario, Canada","['', ('DonaldTrump', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.511, 'neu': 0.489, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9099}",Canada
389,," Chinese officials claiming the #coronavirus was a U.S. bioweapon tested in China. Ok, then.",aranom12,,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), '', ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.845, 'pos': 0.155, 'compound': 0.296}",
390,, #Coronavirus The worlds most expensive joke that you probably won’t get. Prepers aren’t scared.This has really gone crazy.…,DeplorableBugsy,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.3566}",
391,, #EuropeanTravelBan might slow spread of #CoronaVirus short term but smacks of senior presidential aide #StephenMiller cr…,Rich24712803,,"[('EuropeanTravelBan', 'MONEY'), '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), '', ('StephenMiller', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
392,,Bane was a hero #coronavirus ,jonyyz,Lost in Space,"[('Bane', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.455, 'pos': 0.545, 'compound': 0.5574}",Error
393,, Our #FlattenTheCurve graphic is now up on  with proper attribution &amp; a CC-BY-SA licence.  Please share far &amp; wide…,Sorael0,,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.78, 'pos': 0.22, 'compound': 0.5423}",
394,, Important message about #coronavirusuk #coronavirus ,JameswxmGriff,United Kingdom,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.69, 'pos': 0.31, 'compound': 0.2023}",United Kingdom
395,, Watch this video to learn how you can help prevent the spread of respiratory diseases like the novel #coronavirus (#COVID19). T…,FaithHopeLove75,Twilight Zone ,"['', ('COVID19', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.336, 'compound': 0.765}",USA
396,, I’m honestly crying right now as I listen to  speak about the #coronavirus. He is the leader we need.If he wer…,JerzakPaula,,[''],"{'neg': 0.129, 'neu': 0.747, 'pos': 0.124, 'compound': -0.0258}",
397,, Televangelist Jim Bakker is being sued by the state of Missouri for selling fake #coronavirus cures on his website.He claime…,naogannet,,"[('Jim Bakker', 'PERSON'), ('Missouri', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.14, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4767}",
398,, MUST READ: Joe Biden Plagiarizes President ’s #Coronavirus Plan!,crystoldep,"Los Angeles, California, USA","[('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
399,," As a human race we will all get through this! We just have to band together as a community, country, continent, world, as…",justagirrl420,,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",
400,, Here is this week’s #Newscast #coronavirus,dreamingwilly,Sunderland England,"[('week', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",UK
401,," To those who work at DISNEYLAND, LAKERS STADIUM or any event STADIUM that is being closed due to the #coronavirus I wish you…",krisjfer,"Los Angeles, CA","[('DISNEYLAND', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.886, 'pos': 0.114, 'compound': 0.4019}",USA
402,,#Coronavirus Update on 13 March 20 ,TheSoupOfLife,World Wide🌏,"['', ('13 March 20', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",Error
403,, An expert team of nine members with 31 tons of medical supplies from China arrived at Italy on Thursday night (local time).…,Ionexx_RD,San Antonio,"[('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('31 tons', 'QUANTITY'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",USA
