,website,url,headline,entities
0,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,What you need to know,[]
1,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,Arlington National Cemetery will close to visitors beginning Friday,"[('Arlington National Cemetery', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE')]"
2,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,"Brazil's president says he expects results from his coronavirus test ""in the next hours""","[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the next hours', 'TIME')]"
3,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,House plans to move coronavirus bill quickly tonight when an agreement is reached,"[('House', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
4,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,US Southern Command says there are no reports of coronavirus following Brazilian president's visit,"[('US Southern Command', 'ORG'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
5,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,Head coach of English football club tests positive for coronavirus,"[('English', 'NORP')]"
6,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,"Cleveland Cavaliers player donates $100,000 to support staff affected by NBA cancellations","[('Cleveland Cavaliers', 'ORG'), ('100,000', 'MONEY'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
7,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,Illinois issues guidance on large-scale gatherings,"[('Illinois', 'GPE')]"
8,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,Smithsonian Museums and National Zoo close to the public,"[('Smithsonian Museums', 'PERSON'), ('National Zoo', 'ORG')]"
9,CNN,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,School districts across Georgia to close due to the coronavirus,"[('Georgia', 'GPE')]"
10,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"From business to sports to politics, coronavirus reaching into every aspect of daily life",[]
11,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"One hour, three massive stories. On the other side, a different reality for Americans.","[('One hour', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
12,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Chart: See the day-by-day size of the coronavirus outbreak,"[('day', 'DATE')]"
13,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Brazilian official who met Trump at Mar-a-Lago tests positive for coronavirus,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
14,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Staying in due to the coronavirus?  Here's what to stock in your fridge and pantry,[]
15,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Cuba confirms first coronavirus cases, tells people to make their own masks","[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
16,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Coronavirus could 'wreak havoc' on U.S. jails, experts warn","[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
17,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Pence says there's been 'irresponsible rhetoric' from people downplaying the coronavirus,"[('Pence', 'ORG')]"
18,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Coronavirus scammers are seeking to profit off the deadly virus,[]
19,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Trump imposes major restrictions on travel from Europe,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
20,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Map: Confirmed coronavirus cases, worldwide",[]
21,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NCAA limits March Madness attendance as coronavirus hits U.S. athletics,"[('NCAA', 'ORG'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
22,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Dow enters bear territory, plunging by more than 1,400 points","[('more than 1,400', 'CARDINAL')]"
23,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Amid coronavirus spread, health advocates worry Trump's immigration policies put public at risk","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
24,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Asian woman attacked in New York City in possible coronavirus bias crime,"[('Asian', 'NORP'), ('New York City', 'GPE')]"
25,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"On Amazon, fake authors and plagiarized books ride wave of coronavirus interest","[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
26,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,'Cataclysm for our economy': Latin Americans brace for coronavirus impact,"[('Cataclysm', 'ORG'), ('Latin Americans', 'NORP')]"
27,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,People are coming together across U.S. to support local Chinatowns,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Chinatowns', 'PERSON')]"
28,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,New to telecommuting? Here are 8 rules you should follow.,"[('8', 'CARDINAL')]"
29,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Store owner charged after homemade spray sanitizer burns youths,[]
30,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,N.Y. Gov. Cuomo questions low coronavirus test rate,"[('Cuomo', 'PERSON')]"
31,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,'I don't know when I'll see you again': Coronavirus lockdown separates couple married 58 years,"[('58 years', 'DATE')]"
32,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Coronavirus: What you need to know,[]
33,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Photos capture empty cities across the globe,[]
34,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,His team was close to a coronavirus vaccine. Today he told Congress why it's sitting in a freezer.,"[('Today', 'DATE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
35,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Coronavirus patient explains what the illness feels like, conditions in quarantine",[]
36,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Coronavirus updates live: U.S. cases top 1,000","[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('1,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
37,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,New York biotech company works to make antibody treatment for coronavirus,"[('New York', 'GPE')]"
38,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Couple on Grand Princess cruise ship carrying coronavirus patients sues for $1 million,"[('$1 million', 'MONEY')]"
39,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"The U.S. has tested more than 8,500 specimens for coronavirus. That doesn't equal 8,500 patients.","[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('more than 8,500', 'CARDINAL'), ('8,500', 'CARDINAL')]"
40,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Carmakers — and car owners — could soon feel the impact of the coronavirus,[]
41,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Chinese restaurant chain booting diners with fever amid coronavirus outbreak,"[('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
42,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Italians wake up to virtual standstill after sweeping quarantine measures announced,"[('Italians', 'NORP')]"
43,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Coronavirus forces 'Jeopardy!' and 'Wheel of Fortune' to tape without live audience,"[(""'Wheel of Fortune"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
44,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"As coronavirus spreads, students stuck and isolated in epidemic's epicenter",[]
45,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Trump proposes payroll tax cut, other measures to offset coronavirus economic damage","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
46,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Father of coronavirus patient broke quarantine. How can health officials enforce rules?,[]
47,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Latest news for health care. ,[]
48,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"New York's attorney general said Thursday that her office has ordered InfoWar's Alex Jones to immediately stop selling and marketing products as a ""cure"" or ""treatment"" for the coronavirus.","[(""New York's"", 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('InfoWar', 'ORG'), ('Alex Jones', 'PERSON')]"
49,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Some doctors and nurses lack childcare in regions hard hit by the coronavirus, like Seattle. Schools and some day care centers are closing. But they're needed more than ever as the coronavirus continues its spread.","[('Seattle', 'GPE')]"
50,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Unlike employees at Amazon's corporate offices, many fulfillment center employees and delivery drivers cannot carry out their job duties while working from home.","[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
51,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Amazon, like other e-commerce companies, has struggled to police sellers who have sought to take advantage of the panic and flooded online marketplaces with overpriced goods.","[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
52,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Large venues such as Barclays Center and Madison Square Garden will likely be closed for months as officials try to contain the fast-spreading coronavirus.,"[('Barclays Center', 'ORG'), ('Madison Square Garden', 'FAC'), ('months', 'DATE')]"
53,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio is holding a press conference to update the public on the coronavirus outbreak, which has infected 328 people across the state as of Thursday afternoon.","[('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Bill de Blasio', 'PERSON'), ('328', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME')]"
54,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Trump's European travel restrictions could further strain airlines and drive some of them out of business, a trade group warned.","[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
55,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The mayor of Jersey City, New Jersey, implemented a 10 p.m. curfew Thursday for any of the city's establishments that carry a liquor license.","[('Jersey City', 'GPE'), ('New Jersey', 'GPE'), ('10 p.m.', 'TIME'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
56,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""I've said the same thing to you every day for the past three weeks, I think. You are going to see these numbers are going to go up,"" Cuomo said during a press conference Thursday.","[('the past three weeks', 'DATE'), ('Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
57,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""We have to get this testing back. I hate to keep banging on that, but that is such an important piece because we've got know what we're dealing with,"" Atlantic Health CEO Brian Gragnolati told CNBC.","[('Atlantic Health', 'ORG'), ('Brian Gragnolati', 'PERSON'), ('CNBC', 'ORG')]"
58,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"There are currently at least 328 people confirmed cases in New York, Cuomo said, adding that if the state's actual cases were ""10 times that, I would not be surprised.""","[('at least 328', 'CARDINAL'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Cuomo', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
59,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""Unfortunately this virus laid bare the severe shortcomings of the current administration,"" Biden said in front of American flags at an event in Delaware.","[('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Delaware', 'GPE')]"
60,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"European Central Bank (ECB) President Christine Lagarde told CNBC Thursday that her institution was ""fully committed to avoid any fragmentation.""","[('European Central Bank', 'ORG'), ('Christine Lagarde', 'PERSON'), ('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
61,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,New York's Metropolitan Museum of Art announced Thursday it is closing to help contain the spread of the coronavirus.,"[(""New York's"", 'GPE'), ('Metropolitan Museum of Art', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
62,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The decision comes amid a flurry of cancellations and safety measures in the sports world.,[]
63,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson announced a change of strategy to tackle the coronavirus outbreak.,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('Boris Johnson', 'PERSON')]"
64,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""We are talking about it as a patriotic duty,"" Ohio Secretary of State Frank LaRose said in an interview. ""Part of the reason for this is that the demographic that tends to be our poll workers tends to be older.""","[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Frank LaRose', 'PERSON')]"
65,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is self-isolating at home while his wife, Sophie Gregoire, awaits the results of a test for COVID-19, a spokesperson said Thursday.","[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Justin Trudeau', 'PERSON'), ('Sophie Gregoire', 'PERSON'), ('COVID-19', 'PRODUCT'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
66,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The entire country of Italy is shut down as it attempts to slow the coronavirus outbreak and stem a rising death toll. Here's what it looks like.,"[('Italy', 'GPE')]"
67,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The organization also canceled ""all remaining winter and spring"" championships.","[('winter', 'DATE')]"
69,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"A top U.S. health official said the country is ""not really geared"" to conduct the amount of testing for the coronavirus that will be required as the virus continues to spread across the nation.","[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
70,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Lagarde suggested that the coronavirus is likely to keep spreading, despite President Donald Trump's travel ban on some European nations.","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
71,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The U.S. House Oversight and Reform Committee is continuing its hearing Thursday on the country's preparedness and response to the coronavirus outbreak that has swept across the nation.,"[('The U.S. House', 'ORG'), ('Oversight and Reform Committee', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
72,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The Capitol will be closed to the public for the rest of the month, and White House tours will stop indefinitely as officials try to curb the coronavirus pandemic.","[('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('the month', 'DATE'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
73,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The Canadian e-commerce company told employees to work from home starting March 16.,"[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('March 16', 'DATE')]"
74,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""They know nothing. We know more than they do, and that's not acceptable either,"" CNBC's Jim Cramer said.","[('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Jim Cramer', 'PERSON')]"
75,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""I didn't think it was a likely outcome,"" Dallas Mavericks owner Mark Cuban told CNBC on Thursday.","[('Dallas Mavericks', 'GPE'), ('Mark Cuban', 'PERSON'), ('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE')]"
76,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The New York Times' Thomas Friedman said Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates should oversee the efforts to make more test kits and vaccine development.,"[(""The New York Times'"", 'ORG'), ('Thomas Friedman', 'PERSON'), ('Jeff Bezos', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Gates', 'PERSON')]"
77,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The European Central Bank decided not to cut interest rates, despite market expectations for a reduction amid the ongoing coronavirus outbreak.","[('The European Central Bank', 'ORG')]"
